We are looking at Selena
Gomez today, who seems to
have found a perfect balance
between her business empire and
her personal life.
It is a fascinating evolution,
Gary. Her company, Rare Beauty,
is now valued at approximately
two billion dollars. She has
resisted selling it, showing she
is focused on long-term growth
rather than a quick payday.
That level of institutional thinking
is rare in the celebrity
world. She is also using
her platform for something substantial
with Wondermind.
Yes, she is very vocal
about mental health advocacy. Her
Rare Impact Fund has a
goal of raising one hundred
million dollars for services. It
is about de-stigmatizing the conversation
for everyone.
And she is still very
active in her craft. The
buzz from Cannes for Emilia
Pérez is huge.
It really is. She shared
a Best Actress ensemble award
there. She is also preparing
to play Linda Ronstadt in
an upcoming biopic. Between that
and Only Murders in the
Building Season 4 returning August
27th, her schedule is packed.
Yet, she still finds time
for her personal life, sharing
new photos with boyfriend Benny
Blanco just yesterday.
She is truly happy.