Good morning from a slightly
humid South Brooklyn. I am
Gary Thompson, and you are
listening to the morning briefing.
I just finished my commute
over to Jersey City, and
I have to tell you,
the PATH train was packed
today, but it gave me
some time to catch up
on the headlines. Before we
dive into the heavy lifting
of the day, I was
checking in on my guinea
pigs, Pesto and Beans, and
I realized that even in
a quiet house with two
cats and three kids, there
is a certain rhythm to
life that we all try
to maintain. Stability is something
I talk about a lot
on this show. It is
the bedrock of a functioning
society and a functioning life.
And that brings me to
our topic today. We are
looking at someone who has
been in the public eye
for two decades and seems
to have finally found a
balance between her professional output
and her personal stability. I
am talking about Selena Gomez.
Margaret, you have been tracking
the social media movements and
the trade reports over the
last twenty-four hours. What is
the latest on the Gomez
front?
It is a busy window
for her, Gary. If you
looked at Instagram late last
night, June 17th, or early
this morning, June 18th, you
would have seen what she
is calling a life lately
update. It is a series
of photos that really leans
into her relationship with music
producer Benny Blanco. Now, I
know you usually prefer to
stick to the hard economic
data or the rule of
law, but in the world
of entertainment and brand management,
these personal glimpses are strategic
assets. We are seeing her
very publicly happy, which is
a sharp contrast to the
narrative of struggle that defined
her mid-twenties. But beyond the
domestic bliss, we have some
very real movement on her
film career and her business
empire, Rare Beauty.
Let us start with the
work. I have always said
that accountability in your profession
is what earns you a
seat at the table. Gomez
started as a child actor,
moved into pop music, and
now she is being taken
very seriously in rooms that
used to ignore her. The
buzz from the Cannes Film
Festival is still echoing. She
shared a Best Actress ensemble
prize for Emilia Pérez. That
is a Jacques Audiard film,
a musical noir about a
Mexican cartel leader. That is
a long way from the
Disney Channel, Margaret.
It is a massive pivot.
And I will play the
skeptic here for a second,
Gary. Is she a great
actress, or is she a
great celebrity who fits a
specific mold for international directors
looking for American distribution? The
film Emilia Pérez was the
talk of Cannes back in
May, and the momentum hasn't
slowed down. Critics are saying
this is her career-best performance.
But we have to ask,
is this a one-off, or
is she actually transitioning away
from being a pop star?
She told the press recently
that she feels she has
one more album in her
before she wants to settle
into acting full-time.
I respect that. There is
a pragmatism in knowing when
to shift gears. In my
line of work, and in
the lives of the working
families I talk to in
Brooklyn, you have to know
when a certain chapter is
closing so you can invest
in the next one. If
she stays in music just
for the sake of the
charts, she risks burnout. If
she moves into acting and
producing—like she does with Only
Murders in the Building—she is
building long-term equity. Speaking of
that show, we have a
confirmed date for Season 4,
right?
We do. August 27th. The
production has moved to Los
Angeles for part of the
season, which is a big
change for a show that
is so rooted in New
York. But back to your
point about equity, Gary. Let’s
look at Rare Beauty. There
were reports earlier this year,
and reinforced in recent Forbes
analysis, that the company is
being valued in the two-billion-dollar
range. She has resisted the
urge to sell it off
quickly. That shows a level
of institutional thinking that you
usually appreciate. She isn't just
looking for a quick payday;
she’s building a brand that
has stayed relevant for four
years, which is an eternity
in the celebrity makeup world.
It is about the product.
My wife uses some of
those products, and she isn't
someone who buys into celebrity
hype. She buys it because
it works and it is
priced for people who actually
have a budget. That is
the kind of business model
that survives a recession. It
is grounded. Now, Margaret, you
mentioned those photos with Benny
Blanco. You called them strategic.
Explain that to me. I
see a woman in her
thirties posting photos with her
boyfriend. Why is that a
news item for us today?
Because in the last twenty-four
hours, those photos have generated
millions of engagements. In the
digital economy, engagement is currency.
But there is a deeper
layer. For years, the public
narrative around Selena Gomez was
tied to her ex-partners or
her health struggles—her lupus diagnosis
and her kidney transplant. By
being the one to control
the imagery of her current
relationship, she is reclaiming the
narrative. She is saying, I
am not a victim of
my circumstances; I am an
adult in a stable relationship.
However, I’ll throw a curveball
here. Some fans are skeptical
of Benny Blanco. They see
him as a departure from
her usual brand. Is this
a case of a celebrity
trying too hard to seem
relatable by dating someone who
is a bit more of
an eccentric, behind-the-scenes figure?
I think that is overthinking
it, Margaret. People in their
thirties just want someone who
shows up. If he is
a good partner and she
is happy, that contributes to
her professional stability. We see
it in every industry. When
your home life is settled,
your work life flourishes. Look
at her upcoming projects. She
is set to play Linda
Ronstadt in a biopic. That
is a role that requires
immense discipline. Ronstadt was a
powerhouse. If Gomez is going
to pull that off, she
needs to be in a
headspace where she isn't distracted
by tabloid drama.
The Linda Ronstadt project is
interesting because it bridges the
gap between her music past
and her acting future. But
let’s talk about the mental
health aspect. She has her
platform, Wondermind. In the last
few months, she has been
very vocal about the intersection
of mental health and the
workplace. She isn't just posting
platitudes; she is looking at
the economics of wellness. Gary,
you often talk about public
safety and the health of
our communities. Do you think
a celebrity-led mental health platform
actually moves the needle for
a family in Jersey City
or Brooklyn?
It moves the needle if
it de-stigmatizes the conversation. If
a guy working on the
docks or a woman running
a small business sees someone
with that much success admitting
they need help, it makes
it easier for them to
seek help too. It’s about
accountability to oneself. Now, I
want to go back to
the facts of the last
twenty-four hours. We have the
Instagram posts, we have the
ongoing buzz from the Emilia
Pérez trailer, and we have
the Rare Beauty expansion into
body care that is hitting
the UK markets more aggressively
this week. It seems like
she is firing on all
cylinders.
She is. And she is
doing it while navigating the
complexities of being a billionaire—or
near-billionaire—in a climate that is
increasingly hostile to extreme wealth.
She manages to stay likable.
That is a rare feat.
Most people who reach that
level of wealth become disconnected.
But she keeps her focus
on things like the Rare
Impact Fund, which aims to
raise one hundred million dollars
for mental health services. That
is a concrete goal. It
isn't just a vague promise.
That is the rule of
law in action, in a
way. You set a standard,
you create a fund, and
you hold yourself accountable to
the numbers. I like that.
I also like that she
is leaning into her heritage
with the Audiard film. It
is a Spanish-language role. For
a naturalized citizen like me,
seeing someone embrace their roots
while dominating the global stage
is significant. It shows that
the American dream isn't just
about assimilation; it is about
contribution.
It is a bold move,
especially since she has admitted
in the past that her
Spanish wasn't perfect. She put
in the work to be
able to perform in that
language for a major film.
That brings us back to
your favorite theme: the work.
But Gary, let me play
the devil’s advocate. Is there
a risk of overexposure? Between
the cooking shows, the beauty
brand, the hit TV show,
the movies, and the constant
social media updates, are we
reaching a Selena Gomez saturation
point?
There is always that risk.
But as long as the
quality stays high, people will
stay tuned. Only Murders in
the Building is a high-quality
production. It isn't cheap entertainment.
It is well-written and well-acted.
As long as she chooses
projects that have substance, she
avoids the "famous for being
famous" trap. She is famous
for being productive. That is
a distinction that matters to
me.
It’s a fair point. And
looking at the data from
the last twenty-four hours, the
sentiment is overwhelmingly positive. People
are responding to the "life
lately" posts with a sense
of relief. It’s like the
public has been rooting for
her to find this version
of herself. We are seeing
a shift from the "starlet"
to the "mogul."
And that is where we
should leave it. Whether you
are in South Brooklyn or
Central London, the story of
someone putting in the years,
facing their challenges head-on, and
coming out the other side
with a clear vision for
their future is a story
worth following. It is about
the long-term stability we all
strive for. Margaret, thanks for
the breakdown.
Any time, Gary. I’ll keep
an eye on the trades
to see if that Linda
Ronstadt filming schedule gets confirmed.
Sounds good. And I’ll go
check on the guinea pigs.
They probably need more hay.
To our listeners, stay grounded,
stay pragmatic, and we will
talk to you tomorrow. This
has been the morning briefing.