Selena Gomez is dominating the
news cycle today following the
Los Angeles premiere of Wizards
Beyond Waverly Place.
That is right. On October
24, 2024, Gomez hit the
red carpet at the El
Capitan Theatre in a custom
red Rodarte dress. She was
joined by her former co-star
David Henrie to celebrate this
new sequel series.
Gomez is not just guest-starring;
she is an executive producer.
She mentioned her goal is
to provide a safe environment
for the new cast, including
lead actress Janice LeAnn Brown.
It is a significant return
to her roots. The show
hits Disney Channel on October
29 and Disney Plus the
next day. This comes as
she balances a massive career
shift.
Indeed. While she revisits Disney,
she is also gaining serious
Oscar buzz for her role
in the film Emilia Pérez.
Critics are calling her a
frontrunner for Best Supporting Actress.
It is a busy time.
Between her billionaire status from
Rare Beauty and her television
success with Only Murders in
the Building, she is managing
a multi-billion dollar empire while
staying selective with her acting
projects.
She is certainly proving that
a former child star succeeds.