Welcome back. Today we are
looking at the latest search
trends surrounding Selena Gomez as
of May 2024.
That is right. There is
a lot of buzz regarding
her appearance at the Cannes
Film Festival for the movie
Emilia Perez.
People are also searching for
reviews of that specific film
to see how her performance
was received by critics.
Beyond the film industry, there
is significant interest in the
financial side of her career,
specifically the Rare Beauty valuation
news.
It is impressive how she
balances business and acting. We
are also seeing queries about
Only Murders in the Building
Season 4.
Fans are desperate for a
release date. Plus, her personal
life is in the spotlight
with Benny Blanco relationship news
surfacing.
Finally, her ongoing mental health
advocacy continues to be a
major topic of discussion this
month for many people.
It is a busy time
for her across film, television,
business, and her personal life
as well.
We will keep monitoring these
specific search queries to see
what official updates come out
next for the star.
Stay tuned for more updates
on Selena Gomez and her
various projects today.